<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[Yasmine Mustafa]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[Roar For Good]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[Laura Spiekerman]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[Alloy]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[Ellen Weber]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[Temple University]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[Cecily Kellogg]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[Double Good Media]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[Seema Thomas]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[Beah Burger-Lenehan]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[Katy Thorbahn]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[Bobbie Carlton]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[Innovation Women]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[From large public companies to kitchen table startups, companies turn to Bobbie Carlton for help understanding how the worlds of entrepreneurs, startups and innovation intersect with marketing, social media and community building. The creator of Innovation Nights, Bostons beloved social media driven product launch party (more than 800 new products launched), Bobbies background in corporate public relations and marketing allows her to help companies recognize and capitalize on the opportunities presented by the innovation economy and social media driven communities.
Whether your organization wants to think like a startup or connect to the $48.3 billion venture capitalists invested in 4,356 deals in 2014; the HR department is putting in place a recruitment strategy or the VP of Innovation looking to connect with the global startup community, Bobbie can help.
Bobbie Carlton, founder of Carlton PR & Marketing Innovation Nights and Innovation Women, is an award-winning marketing, PR and social media professional, as well as a sought-after speaker, corporate and startup adviser. Bobbie and the Innovation Nights community have helped to launch more than 800 new products which have collectively raised more than $1 billion in funding. Find out more at Innovation Nights. Bobbies latest venture, Innovation Women, is a new online visibility bureau for entrepreneurial, innovative and technical women. Carlton PR & Marketing allows Bobbie to work with a select group of PR & Marketing professionals to support startups and small businesses. Follow Bobbie on Twitter as @BobbieC, @WomenInno @MassInno]]></content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[Jessica Giannasca]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[CHOP]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[Suzanne Gack]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[CHOP]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[Margaret Meadow]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[CHOP]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[Deborah Yogel]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[CHOP]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[Gayle Stidsen-Smith]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[CHOP]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[Kimberly Burress]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[CHOP]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[Kristin Maynes Hayduk]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[PwC]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[Kristen is a Cybersecurity Consultant for PwC Advisory based in Philadelphia, PA. She is a US Army Signal Corps veteran who specialized in Communication Security. 

Before joining PwC in 2008 as an Information Security consultant, Kristen served in the US Army Signal Corps stationed at Schofield Barracks, Hawaii specializing in war-time communications security and cryptography. She started her PwC career performing attack & penetration testing and social engineering. Today, she works with clients in Technology, Telecommunications and Entertainment & Media organizations helping them design, implement and measure the effectiveness of their Cybersecurity program, operating model and architecture. 

She has presented to Board of Directors on the impact of information security and how to prioritize investments to best mitigate risk. Kristen is a Drexel University graduate and holds several information security related certifications.]]></content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[Liv Erickson]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[Liv Erickson is a virtual and augmented reality evangelist and developer at Microsoft. She has experience building for both virtual and augmented platforms, including the Oculus Rift and Meta Glass, and taught an introductory virtual reality development course at the University of Bremens Informatica Feminale summer program this past August. She has previously spoken on virtual reality on the web at JSConf Budapest, and presented two talks on VR technologies at the 2015 Grace Hopper Celebration of Women in Computing.]]></content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[SiNae Pitts]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[AMMO (Amphetamobile, LLC)]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[SiNae Pitts, PhD is Founder and CEO of AMMO, short for Amphetamobile, LLC, a 100% woman-owned mobile technology company in Philadelphia. SiNae is an entrepreneur with a passion for creating user-centric, elegant tech that is online, mobile and good for the world. SiNae earned a PhD in Neuroscience from Columbia University and has published in several peer-reviewed journals and is an avid international foodie and cook. Since the App store opened in Fall of 2008, AMMO has been guided by scientific rigor and understanding of how to present complex information and meaningful use workflows and tools, to bring mobile apps and mobile sites to life. Clients for AMMOs consulting, design, development and licensing include national and international scholarly and medical publishers, such as the New England Journal of Medicine (NEJM), American College of Chest Physicians (CHEST), the World Bank, Thomson Reuters and Elsevier. AMMO's mobile publishing platforms not only include front end, native mobile apps for iOS and Android devices and mobile optimized webs sites, but also easy to use content management systems (CMS's) on the backend.]]></content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[Susan Tabor-Kleiman]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[Eloise Young]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<title><![CDATA[Arushi Srivastava]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[NTT Data]]></company>
		<content><![CDATA[Arushi Srivastava is the Director of Digital Experience practice of NTT DATA Americas. She leads several initiatives around IoT, Analytics, Digital Engagement and Design Thinking. She advises corporate leaders on architecting next generation enterprise solutions which aim at being Social by Design and result in Pervasive Experience.]]></content>
	</node>
</data>
